DIKSHA

9878743369 | dikshapraness38@gmail.com



I'm a quick learner with a knack for mastering new skills. Skilled in communication and leadership, I excel in managing social media platforms like Instagram. I successfully grew two pages, upsc_pathshala to 430k followers since 2017, and Ncertforcivilservices to 158k followers since 2019. My work has attracted opportunities through LinkedIn and direct approaches.

Education

Kurukshetra university

Bachelor of Technology, Electronics and Communication 2010 – 2014

Work Experience

Social Media and Content Manager | UpTodd, Virtual | Nov 2022 - Dec 2023

- 1. Managed Instagram page with 17,000 + followers, having high engagement. increased organic followers by 5 Times.
- 2. Curated blog content targeting parents, increasing readership by 400%
- 3. Oversaw Facebook ad campaigns, optimizing budget allocation
- 4. Worked with influencer marketing processes & impacted the boost of engagement upto 60K+ viewership

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY

Founder & Edtech Influencer- Instagram UPSC_Pathshala & NCERTFORCIVILSERVICES (600K Followers).

- 1. Built the instagram handle from scratch to followers 600K in total from both the pages.
- 2. Made collaborations with brands like Unacademy , Perfection IAS , Prep Aud etc.
- 3. Made high viewership campaign reaching 1.5Mn+ views

TRAININGS

Digital Marketing | Internshala Trainings| Online| Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

•The training consisted of Social Media Marketing, Google Display, Google Search, SEO, Content & Email Marketing, Blogging & Google Analytics.

GENERAL APTITUDE| Internshala Trainings | Online| Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

• Successfully completed a 6 weeks online certified training on General Aptitude. The training consisted of Aptitude evaluation, Reading Comprehension, Quantitative Aptitude, Logical Reasoning, and Data Interpretation modules. In the final assessment, I scored 88% marks.

Created and published my own blog and linked it with Google Analytics. I also added 5+ posts and analysed the traffic in the Google Analytics account.

SKILLS

- Google Analytics, Blogging, Content Marketing, Email Marketing, Search Engine Optimization (SEO), Search Engine Marketing (SEM), Digital Advertising, Display Advertising, Social Media Marketing.
- Social media management and growth
- Content creation and distribution
- Engaging with followers
- Planning and execution
- Revenue generation and optimization
- Effective communication and team leadership